<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourLagos</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="landmark1_name">Lekki Ikoyi Link Bridge</string>
    <string name="landmark1_descript">One of the most notable landmarks in Lagos, the picturesque Lekki Ikoyi Bridge was constructed to offer an alternate route for linking Lekki, Ikoyi, Victoria Island and its environs.</string>
    <string name="landmark1_location">Lekki/Ikoyi axis</string>
    <string name="landmark2_name">Agba Meta</string>
    <string name="landmark2_descript">Agba Meta or Aro Meta) is an Art Deco statue of three Lagos white-cap chiefs located in Lagos, Nigeria.[1] Designed by Bodun Shodeinde in 1991 and standing over 12 ft high, the three sculpted chiefs were built to welcome people coming into Lagos State</string>
    <string name="landmark2_location">Epe</string>
    <string name="landmark3_name">National Arts Theatre</string>
    <string name="landmark3_descript">The National Arts Theatre is the primary centre for the performing arts in Nigeria. The monument is located in Iganmu, Surulere, Lagos. Its construction was completed in 1976 in preparation for the Festival of Arts and Culture (FESTAC) in 1977. The collection of National Gallery of Modern Nigerian Art is housed in a section of this building. Its exterior is shaped like a military hat. It has a 5,000-seater Main Hall with a collapsible stage, and two capacity cinema halls.</string>
    <string name="landmark3_location">Iganmu,Lagos</string>
    <string name="landmark4_name">The New African Shrine</string>
    <string name="landmark4_descript">The New Afrika Shrine is an open air entertainment centre located in Ikeja, Lagos State. It serves as the host location of the annual Felabration music festival.Currently managed by Femi Kuti (eldest son of Fela Kuti) and Yeni Anikulapo-Kuti, it is the replacement of the old Afrika Shrine created in 1970 by Fela Kuti until it was burnt down in 1977. The New Afrika Shrine showcases photo galleries of Fela and music performances by Femi Kuti and Seun Kuti thus making it a tourist attraction.</string>
    <string name="landmark4_location">Agidingbi,Lagos</string>
    <string name="landmark5_name">Badagary Slave Museum</string>
    <string name="landmark5_descript">Badagry Slave Museum and Black History Museum sheds light onto one of the darkest periods in human history and teaches about the heritage left behind. Showing artifacts from the slave trading period, the museum testifies to the cruelty of European traders and their allies and shows the mark they left on mankind. Feel the grim atmosphere on the short, but powerful boat ride to the \"point of no return\" for over half a million souls; and hear all about the individual stories from the past.</string>
    <string name="landmark5_location">Badagary,Lagos</string>
    <string name="landmark6_name">The Five Cowries Terminal</string>
    <string name="landmark6_descript">The Five Cowries Terminal is an ultra-modern and multipurpose twenty-first-century terminal located in Lagos. The facility was built by the largest telecommunications network in Nigeria, MTN Nigeria and donated to the Lagos State Government. The five Cowries terminal was commissioned on August 30, 2018, in a glamorous ceremony organised by MTN.</string>
    <string name="landmark6_location">Ikoyi</string>
    <string name="event1_name">Eyo Festival</string>
    <string name="event1_descript">A regional masquerade festival unique to the city of Lagos, Eyo festival has its root in ancient Yoruba history. The festival features a long procession with participants dressed in white flowing robes which cover their entire body; top hats and sticks, and the masquerades are referred to as “Eyo”. It is usually a 24-day event that takes place in the entire city of Lagos with the sole objective of paying homage to the traditional ruler (Oba) of Lagos. Observers are required to give monetary gifts to the masquerade when he approaches.</string>
    <string name="event2_name">Felabration</string>
    <string name="event2_descript">Felabration is an annual music festival initiated in 1998 by Yeni Anikulapo Kuti, the daughter of the legendary Afro-beat musician late Fela Anikulapo Kuti in memory and celebration of her father within the week of his birthday. The one-week-long event which is held annually at the New Afrika Shrine in Ikeja attracts visitors from different countries and has thus been considered as an official tourist destination by the Lagos State Government. Felabration Festival features musical performances from top music acts from Nigeria and guest appearances from internationally acclaimed musicians and personalities</string>
    <string name="event3_name">The Lagos Marathon</string>
    <string name="event3_descript">The Lagos International Marathon is a bronze label marathon held annually in Lagos, organized by the Athletic Federation of Nigeria. The Marathon course which spans a distance of about 42km, starts at National Stadium, Surulere, Lagos, (where previous half marathons initially finished), is and was preceded by several recurring half marathons held in the city where athletes run the race of endurance to reach the finish line then continues along the Third Mainland Bridge, to the Lekki-Ikoyi link bridge and finishes at Eko Atlantic.</string>
    <string name="event4_name">The Lagos International Trade Fair</string>
    <string name="event4_descript">is the largest international traded exhibition in West Africa held at the magnificent Tafawa Balewa Square, (Race Course) in Onikan, Lagos Island. The Trade Fair is the premier International Trade Fair in Nigeria with the remarkable 10-day event usually starting on the first Friday of November, every year. The fair boasts of approximately five hundred thousand attendees participating in the various sub-sections</string>
    <string name="event5_name">The Lagos Seafood Festival</string>
    <string name="event5_descript">is an annual event in Lagos. The first edition of the festival was held on 10 November 2012 at the exquisite Eko Hotel and Suites. The festival is focused on promoting seafood cuisine culture, local fish production and stimulating investment opportunities in relation to aquaculture and fisheries.</string>
    <string name="restaurant1_name">The Grills Corner</string>
    <string name="restaurant1_descript">The Grill’s Corner is a premium food outlet with a vision to make dining out a fun filled, healthy and different experience . It’s a place where lovers of delicious, always fresh, healthy food can...</string>
    <string name="restaurant2_descript">Atlantic White Bar and Lounge is an edifice situated at the popular Oba Elegushi Private Beach in Lekki, Lagos with a variety of events and facilities to make your stay fun and exciting.</string>
    <string name="restaurant3_descript">XOVAR Lounge (pronounced ‘Zovar’) is a one-stop entertainment centre; with its Indoor/Outdoor Lounge situated on a large expanse of land within the Lekki axis of Lagos</string>
    <string name="restaurant4_descript">Shaunz bar and Lounge is one of the top destination in Lagos for Karaoke + Live Band + Events + Video Games and Club Nites. They offer you a venue to relax and have fun with your friends after work</string>
    <string name="restaurant5_descript">We are a small business unit committed to customer satisfaction and building relationship. For over 15 years, our business affords us the opportunity to serve humanity and do this in the best possible ways</string>
    <string name="restaurant1_location">Shop 20, King Jaja Complex Unilag, Lagos, Nigeria., Lagos, Lagos</string>
    <string name="restaurant2_location">Atlantic White Bar , Elegushi Private Beach, Lekki Lagos, Lagos, Lagos</string>
    <string name="restaurant3_location">19B Sabitex Hotel Drive, Behind Bespoke Event Centre, Opposite House On The Rock, 4th Lekki Roundabout, Lekki Expressway, Lagos,</string>
    <string name="restaurant4_location">27 Sanusi Fafunwa, Victoria Island, Lagos.</string>
    <string name="restaurant5_location">63, Eleshin Street, Obalende-Ikoyi, Lagos, Lagos, Lagos</string>
    <string name="restaurant1_contact">+234 808 111 2211</string>
    <string name="restaurant2_contact">+234 1 811 4950</string>
    <string name="restaurant3_contact">0802 255 2974</string>
    <string name="restaurant4_contact">0709 996 0077</string>
    <string name="restaurant5_contact">+234 816 575 8159</string>
    <string name="restaurant2_name"><![CDATA[Atlantic White Bar & Lounge]]></string>
    <string name="restaurant3_name">Xovar</string>
    <string name="restaurant4_name">Shaunz Nigeria Limited</string>
    <string name="restaurant5_name">Mama Ladi Fast Food Restaurant</string>
    <string name="park1_name">Freedom Park</string>
    <string name="park2_name">Nigerian Conservation Foundation</string>
    <string name="park3_name">Playbarn</string>
    <string name="park4_name">Apapa Amusement Park</string>
    <string name="park5_name">Rosellas Amusement Park</string>
    <string name="park1_descript">Freedom Park is a Memorial and Leisure Park dedicated to the preserving the Lagos colonial heritage and history of the Old Board Street prison, the park also provides venues and the grounds for events and recreational entertainment</string>
    <string name="park2_descript">Nigerian Conservation Foundation is preserving the full range of Nigeria\'s Biodiversity which include species, ecosystems, genetic biodiversity and ideal for recreational park.</string>
    <string name="park3_descript">Playbarn is a Playground and amusement park for children located in Lekki, Lagos.</string>
    <string name="park4_descript">Apapa Amusement Park is an amusement and theme park for children providing them with facilities to engage in sports and recreation, kid\'s rides and gaming experiences</string>
    <string name="park5_descript">Rosellas Amusement Park provides wonderful amusement park, where Families, Schools, Churches, Youth, Corporate bodies and the General Public pay visit to everyday.</string>
    <string name="park1_location">Old Prison Ground Broad Street, Lagos Island, Lagos, Nigeria</string>
    <string name="park2_location">Km 19, Lagos-Epe Expressway, Lekki, Lagos, Nigeria</string>
    <string name="park3_location">14C, Ladipo Omotesho Cole Street, Lekki Phase 1, Lekki, Lagos, Nigeria</string>
    <string name="park4_location">34 Randle Close, Apapa, Lagos Nigeria</string>
    <string name="park5_location">Km 3, LASU-Isheri Road, Rosellas Bus-stop, Igando, Lagos, Nigeria</string>
    <string name="park1_contact">08127556291</string>
    <string name="park2_contact">+234 816 575 8159, +234 817 590 3591</string>
    <string name="park3_contact">0903 111 0077, 0709 996 0077</string>
    <string name="park4_contact">+234 808 111 2211, +234 1 811 4950</string>
    <string name="park5_contact">08037582010</string>
    <string name="placeholder_text">TextView</string>
    <string name="park_contact">0802 255 2974</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">TourLagos</string>
    <string name="landmarkfragment_class_name">LandmarksFragment</string>
    <string name="location_text">Location:</string>
    <string name="parkfragment_class_name">ParksFragment</string>
    <string name="contact_text">Contact:</string>
    <string name="restaurantfragment_class_name">RestaurantsFragment</string>
    <string name="eventfragment_class_name">EventsFragment</string>
    <string name="landmarks_page_title">Landmarks</string>
    <string name="parks_page_title">Parks</string>
    <string name="restaurant_page_title">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="event_page_title">Events</string>
</resources>
